[Music]
well there are three main causes of
cardiovascular diseases in the
philippines the number one reason is
smoking
now the number two reason is unhealthy
diet
and the last reason is the lack of
exercise cardiovascular diseases
according to the department of health
and world health organization are called
right now non-communicable diseases
these are the following stroke
number one heart attack
cancer chronic obstructive pulmonary
disease or copd and diabetes so these
are the five main killers in the country
and for the last two decades
in this negbabago
and that is very alarming number two
makano magpa angioplasty
bypass how many of my patients here may
stroke hindi
the worst thing those who are afflicted
with non-communicable disease
very expensive to get sick right now in
the hospital the cause of medicines have
gone into orbit mal your family's life
will become
miserable so an onsa prevention is
better than a pound of cure
you can plan for your finances you can
plan for your retirement you can plan
for the education of your children but
you can never plan for your health
health max is a health plan that
provides coverage until age 100 so that
you get the funds that you will be
needing for necessary treatment in case
you are diagnosed with a critical
illness right now most people die before
reaching the age of 60 particularly this
generation are dying because of that
communicable diseases in the nakaka
people are not recognizing the risk of
non-communicable diseases aside from the
cause of medicines the lack of
productivity ecommerce
before your retirement period health max
is a very affordable plan for example
a female who is 26 years old can avail
of the 1 million insurance coverage for
only 1 800 per month
the maximum coverage of health max is 10
million pesos and the lowest coverage is
1 million pesos so if you get sick you
have funds if you don't get sick and
there's an untimely death
your family can have funds and if you
don't get sick and at the same time you
live longer you also get funds
the most loving way that you can do for
your family and for yourself is to plan
ahead of time
you have to make sure that you have the
funds that you need in case of medical
emergencies